Doctor,
have you performed subcision?
Yes, we are performing subcision.
I am quite critical when it comes to subcision.
Many people say they had one session
and did not improve.
The truth is that subcision without
filler injection makes no sense.
It is ineffective!
But most of the time,
its effect is the opposite.
During subcision, we must also
inject a monophasic filler,
so that the two tissues that were attached,
and that we separated with subcision,
can heal separately,
with a space between them.
Without filler injection,
the patient's condition will
definitely, definitely get worse.
Proper subcision is one session.